Guide to the Stanford University, Registrar's Office, records SC1288
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Registrar's Office, records
1880-2004
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University. Registrar's Office
SC1288
89.5 Linear Feet (69 boxes)
Conditions Governing Access
Series 4 is restricted until 2022. Series 6, 8, 9 (microfilm), 10, and 12 are restricted for 75 years from date of creation. Otherwise, the materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Arrangement
The records are arranged in 12 series, many of which were previously cataloged under different call numbers.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Administrative transfers: 1968, 1978, 1973, 1984, 1990, 1998, 2001, 2013, 2016.
Scope and Contents
Collection consists of letters to the Office of the Registrar, David Starr Jordan, and Orrin Leslie Elliott; minutes of the Committee on Admissions and Advanced Standing; freshman admission ledgers; grade reports & transcripts on microfilm; and annotated publications produced by the Office of the Registrar.
Universities and colleges -- Administration.; Universities and colleges -- Departments.; Universities and colleges -- Finance.; Cheating (Education).; Stanford University. Registrar's Office; Stanford University. Registrar's Office; Associated Students of Stanford University. Executive Committee.; Angell, Frank; Lathrop, Charles G. (Charles G; Adams, Ephraim Douglass, 1865-1930; Barnes, Earl; Abbott, Nathan, 1854-1941; Young, Allyn Abbott; Stanford University. Registrar's Office; Stanford University. Committee on Graduate Study; Stanford University. Registrar's Office; Elliott, Orrin Leslie; Stillman, John Maxson; Gilbert, Charles Henry; Farrand, Max; Crothers, George E. (George Edward); Jordan, David Starr; Wilbur, Ray L. (Ray Lyman); Leib, Samuel Franklin; Cubberley, Ellwood Patterson; Durand, William Frederick; Matzke, John E. (John Ernst); Branner, John Casper, 1850-1922; Murray, A. T. (Augustus Taber); Hoover, Herbert; Stanford University. Academic Council; Ryan, Harris J. (Harris Joseph); Stanford, Jane Lathrop; Hopkins, Timothy; Marx, Guido H. (Guido Hugo); Show, Arley Barthlow
- Records, 1900-1950; Series 1
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Administrative transfer, 1968; administrative transfer, John Thomas, 1978.
  Scope and Contents
  Records include letters from the Committee on Recommendation of Teachers and from the Appointment Secretary, 1904-1916; the Registrar's letters, 1905-1911; and miscellaneous Registrar's Office documents, 1905-1950. Also includes correspondence 1900-1905 (primarily 1904-1905).
  - The Committeee on Recommendation of Teachers Letters, 1903 February 17 - 1904 June 4 (Box 1)
  - The Committeee on Recommendation of Teachers Letters, 1906 January 19 - 1907 January 25 (Box 1)
  - The Committeee on Recommendation of Teachers Letters, 1907 August 15 - 1908 July 13 (Box 1)
  - Appointment Secretary Letters, 1910 April 27 - 1910 December 6 (Box 1)
  - Appointment Secretary Letters, 1912 June 27 - 1913 March 29 (Box 1)
  - Appointment Secretary Letters, 1916 March 30 - 1916 June 15 (Box 1)
  - Registrar Letters, 1904 September 28 - 1905 May 1 (Box 1)
  - Registrar Letters, 1906 May 29 - 1906 August 27 (Box 1)
  - Registrar Letters, 1907 February 22 - 1907 June 25 (Box 1)
  - Registrar Letters, 1909 May 31 - 1909 August 11 (Box 1)
  - Registrar Letters, 1911 May 31 - 1911 September 28 (Box 1)
  - Registrar Letters, 1914 Feburary 18 - 1914 May 29 (Box 2)
  - Registrar Letters, 1916 March 17 - 1916 May 25 (Box 2)
  - Registrar Letters, 1917 August 9 - 1917 September 18 (Box 2)
  - Registrar Letters, 1918 November 16 - 1919 March 12 (Box 2)
  - Registrar Letters, 1922 May 13 - 1923 August 22 (Box 3)
  - Registrar's Office manual containing various committee minutes applicable to the office, 1905 (Box 3)
  - "Office Bible" containing summaries of student regulations from beginning of Stanford through 1950. Also contains information concerning credits, special student standing, and Stanford University during World War II. (Box 3)
  - Incoming Registrar's Correspondence, 1900 -1902 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Incoming Registrar's Correspondence, 1903 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Incoming Registrar's Correspondence A-B, 1904 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Incoming Registrar's Correspondence C-D, 1904 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Incoming Registrar's Correspondence F-H, 1904 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Incoming Registrar's Correspondence I-L, 1904 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Incoming Registrar's Correspondence M, 1904 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Incoming Registrar's Correspondence N-R, 1904 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Incoming Registrar's Correspondence S, 1904 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Incoming Registrar's Correspondence T, 1904 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Incoming Registrar's Correspondence U-Z, 1904 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Incoming Registrar's Correspondence A-C, 1905 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Incoming Registrar's Correspondence D-G, 1905 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Incoming Registrar's Correspondence H-J, 1905 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Incoming Registrar's Correspondence K-L, 1905 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Incoming Registrar's Correspondence M, 1905 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Incoming Registrar's Correspondence N-R, 1905 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Incoming Registrar's Correspondence S, 1905 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Incoming Registrar's Correspondence T-Z, 1905 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Records, 1983; Series 2 (Accession ARCH-1984-046)
  - Network for Student Information reports, 1983 (Box 1)
- Records, 1891-1928; Series 3 (Correspondence & Clippings)
  The original records in this series were gleaned from a much larger mass of material received and retained by the Registrar's Office during the first four decades of the university's history. The material found in this collection represents that portion deemed most valuable as primary research material or most usefully representative of the larger body of documents. Specific examples include letters from university trustees, faculty, administrators, staff, students, and alumni regarding such matters as admission, grades, class registration, and certification of credits and degrees. General university matters and business concerns are also frequent topics in the correspondence. In addition to two boxes of incoming correspondence, 1891-1913, the collection includes copybooks of outgoing correspondence for 1900-1925, most of which is signed by the registrar. Other items in the collection are correspondence generated by the University Committee on Graduate Study (1912-1915) and by the Student Executive Committee (1900-1915), press clippings concerning Stanford (1924-1928), and memoranda and records concerning cheating, actions of the academic council, and particular scholarships.
  Index to Correspondents in Series 3, Box 1 and 2
  Abbott, Nathan 1 14
  Abbott, Nathan 2 3, 7, 10
  Adams, E. D. 2 10, 12, 15, 18, 21
  Addis, Thomas 2 21
  Alden, Raymond M. 1 21
  Allen, Clifford G. 2 18
  Anderson, Melville B. 1 2, 17
  Angell, Frank 1 2, 17, 21
  Angell, Frank 2 12
  Barnes, Earl 1 2, 4, 10, 14, 21
  Barnes, Mary 1 2
  Barnett, George D. 2 12
  Bassett, Lee Emerson 1 21
  Bassett, Lee Emerson 2 7
  Bergstrom, John A. 2 12
  Bliven, Bruce 2 6
  Branner, John C. 1 17
  Branner, John C. 2 3, 11,15,16
  Bristol, Susan Brown 2 7
  Brun, Samuel J. 1 14
  Caldwell, W. E. 2 11,14,16,19
  Cannon, Henry L. 2 3
  Cathcart, Arthur M. 2 7
  Clark, Frederick C. 1 2
  Clark, George A. 2 9
  Clark, George T. 2 19
  Cleveland, John B. 1 10
  Cooper, William A. 2 12
  Coover, John E. 2 18
  Coover, John E.
  Cornell University 1 20
  Cornell University 2 9
  Cox, Charles E. 1 14
  Cramer, Frank 1 21
  Crawford Albert 2 15, 21
  Crocker, C. J. 1 5
  Crothers, George 1 5, 20
  Crothers, George 2 2, 6, 8, 11, 19
  Cubberley, Elwood P. 1 17, 21
  Cubberley, Elwood P. 2 3, 15, 18
  Curry, David A. 2 11
  Davidson, Percy E. 2 7
  Davis, Horace 2 6, 9, 16
  Dept. of the Interior 2 9
  Dept. of State 2 9
  deYoung, M. H. 2 9
  Dudley, William R. 1 14, 17
  Dudley, William R. 2 12
  Duniway, Clyde A. 1 17
  Durand, William F. 2 10, 12, 21
  Earthquake inquiries 2 4
  Farrand, Max 1 22
  Farrand, Max 2 3, 7, 12, 15
  Foss, John H. 2 12
  Field, Charles K. 2 9
  Flugel, Ewald 1 10, 14
  Franklin, Edward C. 2 10
  Gilbert, Charles H. 1 22
  Gilbert, Charles H. 2 3, 10, 12, 15
  Goebel, Julius 1 10
  Gray, Henry D. 2 7
  Greene, Mrs. F. H. 1 10
  Griffin, James O. 1 10
  Griggs, Edward H. 1 10, 14
  Harper, William R. 1 3, 16
  Hearst, Mrs. Phoebe 1 16
  Hempl, George 1 10
  Gilbert, Charles H. 2 7
  Hoover, Herbert 2 6, 19
  Hopkins, Timothy 1 6, 16, 20
  Hopkins, Timothy 2 6, 9, 11, 14 16
  Hoskins, Leander M. 2 13, 15
  Howard, George E. 1 2
  Howard, J. H. 1 14, 22
  Huberick, Charles H. 2 7, 10
  Hudson, William H. 1 10
  Hull, Charles H. 1 16
  Hunt, Rockwell D. 1 17
  Huston, Charles A. 2 13
  Hutchinson, Joseph 1 14, 22
  Hutchinson, Joseph 2 7
  Jenkins, Oliver P. 1 4
  Jordan, David S. 1 7, 11, 16, 18
  Jordan, David S. 2 2, 6, 9, 16, 19
  Judah, H. R. 1 9, 13
  Kellogg, Vernon L. 1 4, 22
  Krehbiel, Edward 2 15, 21
  Kriehn, George 1 4, 14, 17
  Lathrop, Ariel 1 1
  Lathrop, Ariel
  Lathrop, Charles G. 1 1, 3, 8, 12, 15, 19
  Lathrop, Charles G. 2 1, 5, 9, 11, 14
  Lathrop, Henry 1 2, 17
  Leib, S. F. 2 2, 6, 11
  Lenox, Lionel R. 2 10
  Lesley, Everett P. 2 13, 21
  Long, Royce R. 2 13
  Lovejoy, Arthur O. 1 22
  Marx, Guido 1 14, 22
  Marx, Guido 2 7, 13, 15
  Matzke, John E. 1 4, 22
  Matzke, John E. 2 3, 10, 13
  McDowell, John E. 2 13
  Meyer, Arthur W. 2 13, 18, 21
  Millis, Harry A. 2 7, 18
  Monasch, David 2 11, 16
  Monroe, Will S. 1 2
  Moreno, Halcott C. 2 10, 18
  Murray, Augustus T. 1 10, 17, 22
  Murray, Augustus T. 2 13
  Newcomer, Alphonso G. 2 13
  Ophuls, William 2 18
  Pease, Ernest M. 1 22
  Ponzer, Ernest W. 2 18
  Powers, Harry H. 1 17
  Price, George C. 1 17
  Rendtorff, Karl G. 1 14
  Rice, J. M. 1 3
  Richardson, George M. 1 10
  Rolfe, H. W. 2 13
  Ryan, Harris J. 2 7, 10, 13, 18, 21
  Sabine, George H. 2 18, 21
  Sanford, Fernando 1 2
  Sanford, Fernando 2 13
  Show, Arley B. 1 17, 22
  Show, Arley B. 2 13, 21
  Skinner, Macy M. 2 13
  Smith, James Perrin 1 4, 17
  Snow, William F. 2 13
  Stanford, Jane L. 1 20
  Starbuck, Edwin D. 1 10
  Stillman, John M. 2 13, 15, 21
  Storey, Thomas A. 1 22
  Storey, Thomas A. 2 3, 7
  Stuart, Henry W. 2 18
  Swain, Joseph B. L. 1 2
  Treat, Payson J. 2 13
  U. S. War Department 2 6
  Whitaker, Albert C. 1 22
  Wilbur, Ray Lyman 1 1, 17, 22
  Wilbur, Ray Lyman 2 15, 17, 20
  Wildman, Murray S. 2 21
  Wing, Charles B. 1 2
  Woodward, Frederick C. 2 18
  Young, Allyn A. 2 7, 10, 13
  Young, Stewart W. 2 7
  Young, W. H. 2 18
  Zinsser, Hans 2 15
  - non-faculty, 1891-1892 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - faculty, 1891-1892 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - non-faculty, 1894 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - faculty, 1894 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - non-faculty A-G, 1896 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - non-faculty Hopkins, Timothy, 1896 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - non-faculty Jordan, David Starr, 1896 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - non-faculty Lathrop, Charles E., 1896 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - non-faculty J-W, 1896 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - faculty, 1896 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - non-faculty Jordan, David Starr, 1897 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - non-faculty Lathrop, Charles E., 1897 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - non-faculty, 1897 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - faculty, 1897 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - non-faculty Lathrop, Charles E., 1898-1899 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - non-faculty, 1898-1899 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - faculty, 1898-1899 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - non-faculty Jordan, David Starr, 1901-04 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - non-faculty Lathrop, Charles E., 1901-04 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - non-faculty, 1901-04 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - faculty A-C, 1901-04 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - faculty F-W, 1901-04 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - non-faculty Lathrop, Charles E., 1905 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - non-faculty, 1905 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - faculty, 1905 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Earthquake letters, 1906-07 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - non-faculty Lathrop, Charles E., 1906-07 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - non-faculty, 1906-07 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - faculty, 1906-07 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - non-faculty Crothers, George E., 1908 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - non-faculty, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - faculty, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - non-faculty, 1909-10 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - faculty A-G, 1909-10 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - faculty H-Y, 1909-10 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - non-faculty, 1911 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - faculty, 1911 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - non-faculty, 1912 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - faculty Wilbur, Ray Lyman, 1912 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - faculty, 1912 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - non-faculty, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - faculty Wilbur, Ray Lyman, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - faculty, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Orrin Leslie Elliott, outgoing letters, 1901-1925; 5 bound volumes (Box 3)
  - Graduate Study Committee Correspondence: A-L, 1912-1915 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Graduate Study Committee Correspondence: M-Z, 1912-1915 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Graduate Study Committee Correspondence, 1912-1915 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Graduate Study Committee Correspondence, 1910-1915 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Student Committees' Correspondence, 1910-1915 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Student Committees' Correspondence, 1910-1915 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Student Committees' Correspondence, 1910-1915 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Registrar's Letters (bound), 1903-1904; 2 volume(s) (Box 5)
  - Registrar's Letters (bound), 1906; 1 volume(s) (Box 6)
  - Registrar's Letters (bound), 1907-1909; 2 volume(s) (Box 7)
  - Registrar's Letters (bound), 1912; 2 volume(s) (Box 8)
  - Registrar's Letters (bound), 1914-1915; 2 volume(s) (Box 9)
  - Registrar's Letters (bound), 1915-1919; 2 volume(s) (Box 10)
  - Registrar's Letters (bound), 1919-1920; 2 volume(s) (Box 11)
  - Press Clippings, 1924-1925 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Press Clippings, 1925 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Press Clippings, 1926 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Press Clippings, 1926 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Press Clippings, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Press Clippings, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Press Clippings, 1928 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Academic Council, 1908-1912; Appointment Settings, 1914-1915, 1908-1915 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - California Teaching Recommendations, 1914-1916; Cheating Report, 1915-1916 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee, 1904-1909 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee, 1905-1912 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Limitation of Enrollment of Men, 1915-1916 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Memoranda, 1907-1914 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Questionnaires, 1906-1910 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Dickey and Higley Scholarships, 1908-1915 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Statistics and Enrollment Figures, 1892-1924 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Records, 1937-1947; Series 4 (Accession ARCH-1994-114)
  Minutes of the Committee on Admissions and Advanced Standing, 1937-1947.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until 2022.
  - January 1937 - August 11, 1942 (Box 1)
  - September 25, 1942 - October 1, 1947 (Box 1)
- Records, 1948-1955; Series 5 (Accession ARCH-1998-153)
  Annotated Stanford Registers, 1948-1955. Part I Staff, Students, Summaries - annotations re quarter attended; typed lists of additional and summer students; typed summaries. Part II Courses - annotations re quarter given and number of students.
  - Academic year 1948/49, Part I and II; and 1950/51, Part I and II, 1948-1951 (Box 1)
  - Academic year 1951/52, Part I and II; and 1954/55, Part II only, 1951-1955 (Box 2)
- Records, 1891-1999; Series 6 (Accession ARCH-2013-027)
  Grade reports [microfilm], 1891-1999.
  Restricted for 75 years from date of creation.
  - 1. 1st Semester Reports, 1891-1892; 1 (Box 1)
  - 1. 1st Semester Reports, 1891-1892; 1 (Box 1)
  - 2. 2nd Semester Reports, 1892-1893; 1 (Box 1)
  - 3. 1st Semester Reports, 1893-1894; 1 (Box 1)
  - 4. 2nd Semester Reports, 1893-1894; 1 (Box 1)
  - 5. 2nd Semester Reports, 1894-1895; 1 (Box 1)
  - 6. 1st Semester Reports, 1894-1895; 1 (Box 1)
  - 7. Supplemetary Reports, 1893-1895; 1 (Box 1)
  - 8. 1st Semester Reports, 1895-1896; 1 (Box 1)
  - 9. 2nd Semester Reports (to pg. 157), 1895-1896; 1 (Box 1)
  - 1. 2nd Semester Reports (from pg. 157), 1895-1896; 2 (Box 1)
  - 2. Supplementary Reports, 1895-1896; 2 (Box 1)
  - 3. Summer School in Absentia, 1895-1918; 2 (Box 1)
  - 4. 1st Semester Reports, 1896-1897; 2 (Box 1)
  - 5. 2nd Semester Reports, 1896-1897; 2 (Box 1)
  - 6. 1st Semester Reports (to pg. 179), 1897-1898; 2 (Box 1)
  - 1. 1st Semester Reports (from 179), 1897-1898; 3 (Box 1)
  - 2. 2nd Semester Reports, 1897-1898; 3 (Box 1)
  - 3. Supplementary Lessons, 1897; 3 (Box 1)
  - 4. Supplementary Lessons, 1898; 3 (Box 1)
  - 5. Advanced Senior Reports, 1896-1900; 3 (Box 1)
  - 6. 1st Semester Reports, 1898-1899; 3 (Box 1)
  - 7. 1st Semester Reports, 1899-1900; 3 (Box 1)
  - 1. 2nd Semester Reports, 1898-1899; 4 (Box 1)
  - 2. 2nd Semester Reports, 1899-1900; 4 (Box 1)
  - 3. 1st Semester Reports, 1900-1901; 4 (Box 1)
  - 4. 2nd Semester Reports, 1900-1901; 4 (Box 1)
  - 5. 1st Semester Reports, 1901-1902; 4 (Box 1)
  - 6. 2nd Semester Reports (to Greek I p. 14), 1901-1902; 4 (Box 1)
  - 1. 2nd Semester Reports (from pg. 15), 1901-1902; 5 (Box 1)
  - 2. 1st Semester Reports, 1902-1903; 5 (Box 1)
  - 3. 2nd Semester Reports, 1902-1903; 5 (Box 1)
  - 4. 1st Semester Reports, 1903-1904; 5 (Box 1)
  - 5. 2nd Semester Reports (to Botony pg. 343), 1903-1904; 5 (Box 1)
  - 1. 2nd Semester Reports (Botany pg. 344), 1903-1904; 6 (Box 1)
  - 2. Advanced Senior Reports, 1900-1903; 6 (Box 1)
  - 3. Advanced Senior Reports, 1903-1905; 6 (Box 1)
  - 4. 1st Semester Reports, 1904-1905; 6 (Box 1)
  - 5. 2nd Semester Reports, 1904-1905; 6 (Box 1)
  - 6. 1st Semester Reports (Drawing 4 - pg. 212), 1905-1906; 6 (Box 1)
  - 1. 1st Semester Reports (Drawing 5 - pg. 213), 1905-1906; 7 (Box 1)
  - 2. 2nd Semester Reports, 1905-1906; 7 (Box 1)
  - 3. 1st Semester Reports, 1906-1907; 7 (Box 1)
  - 4. 2nd Semester Reports, 1906-1907; 7 (Box 1)
  - 5. 1st Semester Reports, 1907-1908; 7 (Box 1)
  - 6. 2nd Semester Reports (Geology 3-Rogers), 1907-1908; 7 (Box 1)
  - 1. 2nd Semester Reports (Geology 7b-Smith), 1907-1908; 8 (Box 1)
  - 2. 1st Semester Reports, 1908-1909; 8 (Box 1)
  - 3. 2nd Semester Reports, 1908-1909; 8 (Box 1)
  - 4. Advanced Senior Reports, 1906-1909; 8 (Box 1)
  - 5. 1st Semester Reports, 1909-1910; 8 (Box 1)
  - 6. 2nd Semester Reports (to Princ.Chem.2.Stillman), 1909-1910; 8 (Box 1)
  - 1. 2nd Semester Reports (From Org. Chem.3), 1909-1910; 9 (Box 1)
  - 2. Advanced Senior Reports, 1910-1911; 9 (Box 1)
  - 3. 1st Semester Reports, 1910-1911; 9 (Box 1)
  - 4. 2nd Semester Reports, 1910-1911; 9 (Box 1)
  - 5. 1st Semester Reports, 1911-1912; 9 (Box 1)
  - 6. 2nd Semester Reports (to Surer-Rixford), 1911-1912; 9 (Box 1)
  - 1. 2nd Semester Reports (Surgery-Stillman), 1911-1912; 10 (Box 1)
  - 2. 1st Semester Reports, 1912-1913; 10 (Box 1)
  - 3. 2nd " ", 1912-1913; 10 (Box 1)
  - 4. Advanced Senior Reports, 1911-1913; 10 (Box 1)
  - 5. 1st Semester Reports (Entomology 2-Newcomer), 1913-1914; 10 (Box 1)
  - 1. 1st Semester Reports (Entomology 3-Newcomer), 1913-194; 11 (Box 1)
  - 2. 2nd Semester Reports, 1913-1914; 11 (Box 1)
  - 3. Advanced Senior Reports, 1913-1914; 11 (Box 1)
  - 4. 1st Semester Reports, 1914-1915; 11 (Box 1)
  - 5. 2nd Semester Reports (Entomology McCracken), 1914-1915; 11 (Box 1)
  - 1. 2nd Semester Reports (Entomology 10 McCracken), 1914-1915; 12 (Box 1)
  - 2. Advanced Senior Reports, 1915-1916; 12 (Box 1)
  - 3. 1st Semester Reports, 1915-1916; 12 (Box 1)
  - 4. 2nd Qtr. Reports, 1915-1916; 12 (Box 1)
  - 5. Advanced Senior Reports, 1915-1916; 12 (Box 1)
  - 6. 1st Semester Reports (German 23-Cooper), 1916-1917; 12 (Box 1)
  - 1. 1st Semester Reports (German 23 Rentdorff), 1916-1917; 13 (Box 1)
  - 2. 2nd Semester Reports, 1916-1917; 13 (Box 1)
  - 3. Advanced Senior Reports, May-17; 13 (Box 1)
  - 4. Autumn Quarter Reports, 1917-1918; 13 (Box 1)
  - 5. Winter " " (Mech. Engr. 6A - Stanley), 1917-1918; 13 (Box 1)
  - 1. Winter Quarter Reports (Mec. Engr. 6B Stanley), 1917-1918; 14 (Box 1)
  - 2. Spring Quarter Reports, 1917-1918; 14 (Box 1)
  - 3. Summer " ", 1917-1918; 14 (Box 1)
  - 4. Advanced Senior Reports, 1918; 14 (Box 1)
  - 5. Autumn Quarter Reports, 1918-1919; 14 (Box 1)
  - 6. Winter " ", 1918-1919; 14 (Box 1)
  - 1. Spring Quarer Reports, 1918-1919; 15 (Box 1)
  - 2. Summer Quarter Reports, 1918-1919; 15 (Box 1)
  - 3. Senior Reports, Jun-19; 15 (Box 1)
  - 4. Autumn Quarter Reports, 1919-1920; 15 (Box 1)
  - 5. Winter Quarter Reports (Physics 18-Rogers), 1919-1920; 15 (Box 1)
  - 1. Winter Quarter Reports (Psychology 6 Martin), 1919-1920; 16 (Box 1)
  - 2. Spring Quarter Reports, 1919-1920; 16 (Box 1)
  - 3. Summer " ", 1919-1920; 16 (Box 1)
  - 4. Advanced Reports, Jun-20; 16 (Box 1)
  - 5. Autumn Quarter Reports (Phy. Tr.-Brown), 1919-1920; 16 (Box 1)
  - 1. Winter Quarter Reports (Phys. Ed. Bunting), 1920-1921; 17 (Box 1)
  - 2. Spring Quarter Reports, 1920-1921; 17 (Box 1)
  - 3. Summer " ", 1920-1921; 17 (Box 1)
  - 4. Med. School Reports, 1920-1921; 17 (Box 1)
  - 5. Adv. Senior Qtr. Reports, Jun-21; 17 (Box 1)
  - 6. Autumn Quarter Qtr. Reports (Psych 6 Trace), 1921-1922; 17 (Box 1)
  - 1. Autumn Quarter Reports (Psych. 7 Coover), 1921-1922; 18 (Box 1)
  - 2. Winter Quarter Reports, 1921-1922; 18 (Box 1)
  - 3. Spring Qtr. Reports, 1921-1922; 18 (Box 1)
  - 4. Summer Qtr. Reports, 1921-1922; 18 (Box 1)
  - 5. Med. School Reports, 1921-1922; 18 (Box 1)
  - 6. Autumn Quarter Reports, 1922-1923; 18 (Box 1)
  - 1. Winter Quarter Reports, 1922-1923; 19 (Box 1)
  - 2. Spring Quarter Reports, 1922-1923; 19 (Box 1)
  - 3. Summer " ", 1922-1923; 19 (Box 1)
  - 4. Med. School Qtr. Reports, 1922-1923; 19 (Box 1)
  - 5. Adv. Senior Qtr. Reports, 1922; 19 (Box 1)
  - 6. Adv. Qtr. Reports (M.E. 6 Stanley), 1923; 19 (Box 1)
  - 1. Advanced Senior Reports (M.E.7-Palmateer), 1923; 20 (Box 1)
  - 2. Autumn Quarter Reports, 1923-1924; 20 (Box 1)
  - 3. Winter Qtr. Reports, 1923-1924; 20 (Box 1)
  - 4. Spring Qtr. Reports, 1923-1924; 20 (Box 1)
  - 5. Summer Qtr. Reports, 1923-1924; 20 (Box 1)
  - 6. Med. School Qtr. Reports (to Surgery 218 B), 1923-1924; 20 (Box 1)
  - 1. Med. School Reports (from Surgery 128), 1923-1924; 21 (Box 1)
  - 2. Advanced Senior Reports, 1924; 21 (Box 1)
  - 3. Autumn Quarter Reports, 1924-1925; 21 (Box 1)
  - 4. Winter Qtr. Reports, 1924-1925; 21 (Box 1)
  - 5. Spring Qtr. Reports (Psychology 275-Strong), 1924-1925; 21 (Box 1)
  - 1. Spring Quarer Reports (Psychology 280-Terman), 1924-1925; 22 (Box 1)
  - 2. Summer Quarter Reports, 1924-1925; 22 (Box 1)
  - 3. Med. School Reports, 1924-1925; 22 (Box 1)
  - 4. Adv. Senior Reports, Jun-25; 22 (Box 1)
  - 5. Autumn Quarter Reports, 1925-1926; 22 (Box 1)
  - 6. Winter " " (Pol. Science 240), 1925-1926; 22 (Box 1)
  - 1. Winter Quarter Reports (Political Science 242), 1925-1926; 23 (Box 1)
  - 2. Spring Quarter Reports, 1925-1926; 23 (Box 1)
  - 3. Summer " ", 1925-1926; 23 (Box 1)
  - 4. Advanced Senior Reports, Jun-26; 23 (Box 1)
  - 5. Med. Reports, 1925-1926; 23 (Box 1)
  - 6. Autumn Quarter Reports, 1926-1927; 23 (Box 1)
  - Anesthetics 1924-1925 filmed at beginning of reel, 1925-1926; 23 (Box 1)
  - 1. Autumn Quarter Reports, 1926-1927; 24 (Box 1)
  - 2. Winter Quarter Reports, 1926-1927; 24 (Box 1)
  - 3. Spring Quarter Reports, 1926-1927; 24 (Box 1)
  - 4. Summer Quarter Reports (Chemistry 128-Bergstrom), 1926-1927; 24 (Box 1)
  - From Chem 1,2 to end Sum. 26-27 (refilmed on R. 30), 24 (Box 1)
  - 1. Summer Quarter Reports (Chemistry 141), 1926-1927; 25 (Box 1)
  - 2. Autumn Quarter Reports, 1927-1928; 25 (Box 1)
  - 3. Winter Qtr. Reports, 1927-1928; 25 (Box 1)
  - 4. Spring Qtr. Reports (Phys. Ed, H#1-Long), 1927-1928; 25 (Box 1)